<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Faith on Words of Praise</title>
    <link>danielakproh.github.io/faith/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Faith on Words of Praise</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 15:33:32 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="danielakproh.github.io/faith/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The LORD Is My Rock</title>
      <link>danielakproh.github.io/faith/the-lord-is-my-rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 15:33:32 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>danielakproh.github.io/faith/the-lord-is-my-rock/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I love you, LORD, my strength.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The LORD is my rock, my fortress and my deliverer; my God is my rock, in whom I take refuge, my shield and the horn of my salvation, my stronghold.&#xA;I called to the LORD, who is worthy of praise, and I have been saved from my enemies. The cords of death entangled me; the torrents of destruction overwhelmed me. The cords of the grave coiled around me; the snares of death confronted me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Pleasant it is to Dwell Together in Unity!</title>
      <link>danielakproh.github.io/faith/song-of-degrees-133/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 00:15:48 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>danielakproh.github.io/faith/song-of-degrees-133/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BEHOLD, how good and how pleasant &lt;em&gt;it is&lt;/em&gt; for brethren to dwell together in unity! &lt;em&gt;it is&lt;/em&gt; like the precious ointment upon the head, that ran down upon the beard, &lt;em&gt;even&lt;/em&gt; Aaron&amp;rsquo;s beard: that went down to the skirts of his garments; as the dew of Hermon, &lt;em&gt;and as the dew&lt;/em&gt; that descended upon the mountains of Zion: for there the LORD commanded the blessing, &lt;em&gt;even&lt;/em&gt; life for evermore.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Will Love Thee</title>
      <link>danielakproh.github.io/faith/i-wil-love-thee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 08:34:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>danielakproh.github.io/faith/i-wil-love-thee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I Will love thee, O LORD, my strength. The LORD &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; my rock, and my fortress, and my deliverer; my God, my strength, in whom I will trust; my buckler, and the horn of my salvation, &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; my high tower.&#xA;I will call upon the LORD, &lt;em&gt;who is worthy&lt;/em&gt; to be praised: so shall I be saved from mine enemies. The sorrows of death compassed me, and the floods of ungodly men made me afraid. The sorrows of hell compassed me about: the snares of death prevented me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All Praise to You O Lord</title>
      <link>danielakproh.github.io/faith/all-praise-to-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 20:51:34 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>danielakproh.github.io/faith/all-praise-to-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;O Lord, how majestic is Your name in all the earth! You are the Creator of the heavens and the earth, the One who spoke light into existence with a Word. By Your breath, the stars were flung into the expanse, each one declaring Your glory and craftsmanship. You are the Alpha and the Omega, the beginning and the end, the Starter and Finisher, the Eternal One who transcends time and space. Before the mountains were brought forth, before the seas roared their praise, You were God, enthroned in majesty, clothed in light, and surrounded by the unending chorus of heavenly beings who shout: &amp;ldquo;Holy, holy, holy is the Lord God Almighty; the whole earth is full of His glory!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
