<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Words of Praise</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Words of Praise</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 12:36:29 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rotational Motion: Movement in Circle</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/rotational-motion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 12:36:29 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/rotational-motion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-what-is-an-angle&#34;&gt;I. What is an Angle?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-hello&#34;&gt;1. hello&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;11-heyy&#34;&gt;1.1 heyy&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before we tackle rotation, we first need to understand its elementary foundation which is an &lt;em&gt;angle&lt;/em&gt;. An angle is a portion of a circle. &amp;ldquo;Measuring an angle&amp;rdquo; is assigning a value to that &lt;em&gt;circular portion&lt;/em&gt;. The thing is, an angle does not appear magically though, it starts somewhere-just like anything in life has a beginning and also an end.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s say you decide to take a walk on a circle. You will first stand at a particular spot, then start walking. Let&amp;rsquo;s call that starting point A. As you start walking, you realize that you need a break and stop for a second-this is position B&amp;mdash;that&amp;rsquo;s our position B.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Will Love Thee</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/i-wil-love-thee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 08:34:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/i-wil-love-thee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I Will love thee, O LORD, my strength. The LORD &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; my rock, and my fortress, and my deliverer; my God, my strength, in whom I will trust; my buckler, and the horn of my salvation, &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; my high tower.&#xA;I will call upon the LORD, &lt;em&gt;who is worthy&lt;/em&gt; to be praised: so shall I be saved from mine enemies. The sorrows of death compassed me, and the floods of ungodly men made me afraid. The sorrows of hell compassed me about: the snares of death prevented me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All Praise to You O Lord</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/all-praise-to-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 20:51:34 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/all-praise-to-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;O Lord, how majestic is Your name in all the earth! You are the Creator of the heavens and the earth, the One who spoke light into existence with a Word. By Your breath, the stars were flung into the expanse, each one declaring Your glory and craftsmanship. You are the Alpha and the Omega, the beginning and the end, the Starter and Finisher, the Eternal One who transcends time and space. Before the mountains were brought forth, before the seas roared their praise, You were God, enthroned in majesty, clothed in light, and surrounded by the unending chorus of heavenly beings who shout: &amp;ldquo;Holy, holy, holy is the Lord God Almighty; the whole earth is full of His glory!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
